

SZABÓ ATTILA

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Phone +421 911 297 305

Email tailorstile@gmail.com

Website https://attilaszabo.github.io/

Address Slovakia Vozokany 379/17

SKILLS

- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- JAVASCRIPT

LANGUAGES

- HUNGARIAN
- SLOVAK
- GERMANY
- ENGLISH

ABOUT ME

I started my web development career on 1.1.2021. Whatever difficulties there were during my studies, I successfully took them. In the last 1 year, I also built my portfolio, which was uploaded to my Git-hub page. Whatever difficulty I face, I successfully overcome it.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Wertheim 2007-2012

GROUP LEADER

Completing the weekly tasks and assigning work. Management and assignment of 3 shifts. Reconciliation of hours worked with employees. Solving possible technical problems.

Linditex 2012-2022

BUSINESS CLERK

Addressing potential clients, attending personal meetings. Development of price offers. Contact with customers. In case of problems, online or personal meeting.

EDUCATION

2004-2007 Vocational secondary school

2015-2017 **Accounting and economics.**Accounting